Atom {
	Name = "KartaVR Hotkeys",
	Category = "KartaVR/Hotkeys",
	Author = "Andrew Hazelden",
	Version = 4.03,
	Date = {2019, 10, 12},
	Description = [[<p>The <a href="http://www.andrewhazelden.com/projects/kartavr/docs/hotkeys.html">KartaVR Hotkeys</a> file allows you to increase your productivity when doing complex 360VR stitching, paint/roto repair, effects, and compositing in Fusion and Resolve by reducing many tasks to a single keypress.</p>

<h2>Hotkey Considerations</h2>

<p>To avoid possible keyboard mapping hotkey conflicts, the KartaVR hotkeys file is a KartaVR atom package that does not get installed automatically by the default Reactor based "KartaVR" atom package installation process. If you want to have the custom KartaVR hotkeys available to you, you need to specifically to select the "KartaVR Hotkeys" atom package in Reactor, and click the "install" button to add it. You then need to restart Fusion Standalone/Resolve once in order for the .fu file to be loaded as your part of your active hotkey set.</p>

<p><i>If you also use the <a href="https://github.com/statixVFX/nuke2fusion">nuke2fusion</a> Reactor atom package on your system, you will want to edit one of the two hotkey sets to avoid overlapping use of hotkeys like TAB and a few other single key-press based hotkeys that are active when the Fusion Nodes (Flow) view area is "in focus" and is the active context.</i></p>

<p>The "KartaVR Hotkeys.fu" file is installed by Reactor to:<br>
<a href="file://Reactor:/Deploy/Config/">Reactor:/Deploy/Config/</a></p>

<h2>How to Edit a .fu Hotkeys Entry</h2>

<p>If you want to comment out an individual Fusion .fu hotkey file's "single line" hotkey entry, in  either "nuke2fusion.fu" or "KartaVR Hotkeys.fu", simply add a "Lua programming language" style pair of two adjacent dashes like "--" to the start of that individual hotkey entry line in your .fu file. As an example, you could comment out the KartaVR PanoView "TAB" hotkey entry using this type of edit on the .fu file:

<pre>-- TAB = "RunScript{filename = 'Scripts:/Comp/KartaVR/Viewers/PanoView.lua'}",</pre>

<h2>FU Scanner Will Find Your Hotkeys</h2>

<p>Reactor v3.14 has added a new built-in tool called "Fu Scanner" that lets you track down all of the installed .fu files in your "Config:/" PathMap based folders. This Fu Scanner script can be accessed from the "Reactor > Tools > Fu Scanner" menu item in Fusion Standalone. In Resolve this script is located at "Workspaces > Scripts > Reactor > Tools > Fu Scanner".</p>

<p>If you are still running a "Config:/Reactor.fu" file that was installed with the original Reactor v1.x or v2.x Reactor installer scripts from 2018, you wont see the root level menu entry for the Fu Scanner tool inside of Fusion Standalone. In that case you should either upgrade your "Reactor.fu" file by running the Reactor Installer v3 script, or failing that, simply run to the "Script > Reactor > Tools > Fu Scanner" menu item.</p>

<h2>KartaVR Technical Support</h2>
<p>Tech support is available through the following "Steak Underwater" user community thread. A free WSL forum login is required to see the inline images on this webpage, and to be able to post a new message on the topic.<br>
<a href="https://www.steakunderwater.com/wesuckless/viewtopic.php?p=21111#p21111">WSL Forum | Reactor | Reactor Submissions | KartaVR v4 Freeware Edition Thread</a><br>
<i>(Protip: If you are serious about mastering Fusion or Resolve, the Steak Underwater forum is essential to your success!)</i></p>

<h2>Email Andrew Hazelden</h2>
<p><a href="mailto:andrew@andrewhazelden.com">andrew@andrewhazelden.com</a></p>

]],
	Deploy = {
		"Config/KartaVR Hotkeys.fu",
	},
}
